realitytvworld.com 2018-11-26

# Reality TV World Privacy Policy @ Reality TV World - News, information, episode summaries, message boards, chat and games for unscripted television programs

[HOME](http://www.realitytvworld.com/) > [Reality TV World Privacy Policy](http://www.realitytvworld.com/realitytvworld/privacy.shtml)

Your privacy is important to us. This page is used to inform website visitors regarding our policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information for users of our Service, the Reality TV World website. 

If you choose to use our Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation with this policy. The Personal Information that we collect are used for providing and improving the Service. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy. 

INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE 

For a better experience while using our Service, we may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information, including but not limited to your name, email address, and phone number. The information that we collect will be used to contact or identify you. Reality TV World collects information from our users at several different points on our website. 

LOG DATA 

We want to inform you that whenever you visit our Service, we collect information that your browser sends to us that is called Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser version, pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, and other statistics. 

COOKIES 

Cookies are files with small amount of data that is commonly used an anonymous unique identifier. These are sent to your browser from the website that you visit and are stored on your computer's hard drive. Our website uses these cookies to collection information and to improve and operate our Service. By continuing to visit and use our website you agree to our use of cookies. 

Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. 

In order to better serve you and improve the user experience, we are analyzing the audience of our site with [ Web Analytics](https://www.afsanalytics.com/info/105/web-analytics-how-it-works.html) solution: [ AFS Analytics ](https://www.afsanalytics.com/). This service, which complies with the general data protection regulations, may save personal data (as defined by the GDPR) as a subcontractor, including a unique number consisting of alphanumeric characters identifying you. This encrypted data is saved on secure servers located in France or in Canada. Canada guarantees data protection under Articles 44 and 46 of the GDPR. No banking information is transmitted to AFS Analytics. We are the sole owner of the personally identifiable or not information data collected on our website. AFS Analytics does not share, sell, or claim any rights to this data. The storage duration is limited to 365 days by default. You may request the deletion or modification of this data by contacting our Data Manager or [DataSense](https://www.datasense-analytics.com/), the company responsible for data for AFS Analytics. For collecting data, we are using [analytics.js](https://www.afsanalytics.com/info/113/add-analytics-js-to-your-website.html), a library developed by AFS Analytics. This library uses cookie technology. The cookies are exclusively attached to our domain name, first-party Cookies and are not shared . The data collected makes it possible to provide statistical traffic data. We are the sole owner of these cookies, and you can oppose their registration: Click here to opt out of AFS Analytics cookies 

SERVICE PROVIDERS 

We may employ third-party companies and individuals for numerous reasons, including the following: 

\- To facilitate our Service;   
\- To provide the Service on our behalf;   
\- To perform Service-related services; or   
\- To assist us in analyzing how our Service is used. 

We want to inform our Service users that these third parties have access to your Personal Information. The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf. However, they are obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose. 

THIRD PARTY ADVERTISING 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site, including Exponential Interactive, Google, PixFuture, DoubleClick, Sovrn, AdSupply, Trion, RevContent, Zergnet,  and other third-party advertising companies. 

These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). Click [here](http://www.doubleclick.com/us/corporate/privacy/) to view [DoubleClick's privacy statement](http://www.doubleclick.com/us/corporate/privacy/). 

Exponential Interactive, Inc, as our partner, have a legitimate interest to collect and profile personal data in the form of IP address and cookie ID from users on our website in order to provide targeted online advertising and ad measurement. For more details including opt-out requests, access requests or complaints, please review their [privacy policy](http://exponential.com/privacy/) or contact their data protection officer via [privacy@exponential.com](mailto:privacy@exponential.com). 

Below are the details of Exponential Interactive's cookie: 

SHARING 

We may share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. 

SECURITY 

We value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

MESSAGE BOARDS 

In order to use our message boards an valid email address must be provided to confirm registration. Additionally, our message board may have active a feature that allows a registered message board user, when viewing any posting of another user, to click on a EMAIL icon mext to the poster's username and send them a private email. In order to be able to send this private email, a new message dialog from the user's email program may appear on their screen in which the poster's email address may be visible to the user. If you are looking for full anonymity, please DO NOT POST as full anonymity is not currently available nor guaranteed with respect to message board postings. 

LINKS TO OTHER SITES 

Our Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by us. Therefore, we strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services. 

EMAIL NEWSLETTER 

If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. 

SURVEYS & CONTESTS 

From time-to-time our site may request information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. 

TELL-A-FRIEND 

If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend’s name and email address. Reality TV World will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. Reality TV World stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email. 

SPECIAL OFFERS 

We send new registered members a welcome email to verify password and username. Established members may also occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see our choice and opt-out below. 

SITE AND SERVICE UPDATES 

We may also send users site and service announcement updates. Members may not be able to un-subscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via email. 

CHOICE/OPT-OUT 

Our users are given the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information. Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials from our partners may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to unsubscribe in the subject line in the email or email us at feedback@realitytvworld.com. Users of our site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether they should proceed with services that require an outside party, or not. 

CHILDREN'S PRIVACY 

Our Services do not address anyone under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from children under 13. In the case we discover that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we immediately delete this from our servers. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact us so that we will be able to do necessary actions. 

CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY 

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, we advise you to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes are effective immediately, after they are posted on this page. 

CONTACT US 

If you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.
